

# Proshanta Halder

Software Engineer | Full Stack



I have been working as a webapp developer from 2017. Laravel and Codeigniter is my core coding framework for PHP. I also have expertise on HTML5, CSS3(Bootstrap 4), JavaScript(JQuery, Ajax, React, React Native). I like to code and love my work. I can develop satisfactory product as per your requirement and choice. I can speak in English, Bengali (Mother tongue) without any problem.



(+880)-1749717065



shantohalder63@gmail.com



Brammonkitta, Keraniganj, Dhaka-1310



## Software engineer skills

- 1) Communication
- 2) Teamwork
- 3) Computer programming and coding
- 4) Problem-solving
- 5) Multitasking



## Programming skills

PHP,JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3, SASS(SCSS), BootStrap3-4, Git, Codeigniter, Laravel, React Native MySQL, MongoDB.



## Social Presence

- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/ in/proshanta-halder-369b68139/

Youtube
 https://www.youtube.com/cha
 nnel/UC2D3Ltj0vVqQjDSInsurmNg

- Github https://github.com/shanto027



# **Employment Records**

Software Engineer @Cyberdyne Technology Ltd.

NOV 2020 - Currently Working

\* Responsible for leading software development.

#### Software Engineer @Be Yourself Ventures Ltd.

FEB 2020 - OCT 2020

Worked in very large scale Mobile Tripzchat Application application from scratch as a Full Stack Developer. Mainly used Javascript React Native Framwork • Lead development in both backend and front end developers

#### Lead Software Engineer @Crashedeal Ltd.

DEC 2018 - FEB 2020

Worked mainly in a large scale web based discount deal management application using PHP MVC (Codeigniter) SQL server.

## Assistant Programmer @Innovative Soft

FEB 2017 - DEC 2017

Media monitoring is the act of tracking topics across print, online, and broadcast media output.

#### Web Designer@Creative IT Institute

APR 2015 - MAR 2016

Design theme for themeforest psd to html content as a web designer



# Education

Computer Science and Engineering @Daffodil Institute of IT JAN 2013 - Mar 2017



# Personal

Date of birth: 06 March, 1995 Nationality: Bangladeshi Language: English, Bengali



# **Previous Work**

## Web Application

- 1) https://www.napleshomeinsurancefl.com
- 2) https://crashedeal.com
- 3) http://elorasharee.com/
- 4) http://odoctorsbd.com/
- 5) http://tourplanbd.com/
- http://cyberdynebd.com/pms
  School Management Software
- 8) Media Monitoring Web Application

## Mobile Application

- 1) https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.byvl.tripzchat
- 2) https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.easyquiz
- 2) https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.crashedeal

The above mentioned information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief. If I am selected and given a chance to serve in your esteemed organization I shall prove my best.